<data><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>15 facts about sea level rise that should scare the hell out of you</theme><text>I'm recently back from the Marshall Islands -- one of the low-lying Pacific island nations that literally could be wiped off the map by climate change and rising seas.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>The world's critically endangered species</theme><text>The world's animal population has halved in 40 years as humans put unsustainable demands on Earth, according to a 2014 report from the World Wide Fund for Nature.</text><duplication>7.69230769231</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Al Jazeera journalist arrested in Berlin</theme><text>The Qatar-based Al Jazeera network is calling on German authorities to release a journalist arrested in Berlin and wanted in Egypt.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Al Shabaab claims responsibility for Somalia suicide attack</theme><text>A suicide bomber rammed a car packed with explosives into the entrance of a Somali intelligence training center Sunday, a government official said.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Stowaway falls from British Airways plane</theme><text>A stowaway on a British Airways jet was found dead after falling on a roof as the plane approached London Heathrow Airport, authorities said Friday.</text><duplication>6.06060606061</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>India ties itself in knots over International Yoga Day</theme><text>The Sanskrit word "yoga" may mean union but, for some in India, yoga has never been more divisive.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Johnny Depp's 'private village' up for sale at $26 million</theme><text>Known for his swashbuckling role in the "Pirates of the Caribbean" movies, actor Johnny Depp has put one of his most treasured items on the market.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>$3.4 billion worth of art in a little corner of Switzerland</theme><text>Art Basel is a behemoth. Think of it as the ultimate superstore of the art market with its endless aisles and swarms of shoppers. The annual event that bears the clich&#233; distinction "mother of all art fairs" is in its 46th year, open for business now through June 21 in its namesake Swiss hometown. It features 300 or so international exhibiting galleries hailing from five continents, and reportedly $3.4 billion worth of art. And if it's anything like it was last year, it will draw a crowd of more than 92,000 people over the course of the week-long event.</text><duplication>1.16959064327</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Why does this man want you to wash with oil?</theme><text>If you thought vegetable oil was only for cooking, think again. In Lusaka, Zambia, one entrepreneur is converting used oil into fuel and soap.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>How to look like this on $100 a month</theme><text>Meet Lourens "Loux" Gebhardt -- a viral sensation from Namibia using social media to teach men how to dress.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Paying a premium for green in England</theme><text>The grounds of the Medmenham Abbey in Buckinghamshire, England, could easily be the set of a romanticized period drama.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Friend or food? Dog meat trade divides China</theme><text>Yulin's dog meat "festival," where some 10,000 dogs are slaughtered and served up as meals, is often wrongly assumed to be an ancient Chinese tradition.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Refugee numbers reach highest ever recorded</theme><text>There are more refugees in the world today than ever documented and more than half are children.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Soccer players fired over Thai orgy</theme><text>Three players for English football club Leicester City, including the son of the club's manager, have been sacked after video surfaced of them apparently participating in a racist orgy on the team's recent Thai tour.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Chad strikes Boko Haram in Nigeria, bans burqas</theme><text>The central African country of Chad conducted airstrikes against Boko Haram sites in neighboring Nigeria on Wednesday and announced it has banned burqas, the head-to-toe garment worn by some Muslim women, after twin bombings earlier this week by veiled attackers.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Sister from missing UK family makes contact</theme><text>CNN's Nic Robertson says a sister from the missing family in Bradford, England has made contact by phone but may already be in Syria.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Iraqi Sunni soldiers graduate amid complaints</theme><text>"They're over there," the provincial official said, winking and motioning with his head toward a group of men in khaki uniforms huddled around a black Humvee.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>See inside an ISIS security building</theme><text>CNN's Arwa Damon visits an ISIS security building in the recently liberated Syrian town of Tal Abyad.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Russia opens 'military Disneyland'</theme><text>CNN's Matthew Chance visits a park outside Moscow where families get the chance to play around with tanks, missile launchers and other assorted Russian military hardware.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>5 powerful quotes from Pope's encyclical</theme><text>Here are some of the most powerful quotes from Pope Francis' encyclical on the environment released Thursday:</text><duplication>10.0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>How a scientist in a parking lot may have influenced the Pope and climate change</theme><text>Professor Veerabhadran Ramanathan is a man of science who deals in data-driven evidence and provable facts, but he is absolutely convinced religion is the key to stopping global warming.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>The Pope's life-embracing, anti-digital media sermon</theme><text>The latest zeitgeist commentary from that keen social observer and populist pundit, Pope Francis, has arrived like an Easter egg, hidden inside a larger basket of criticism focused on climate change. The Pope's 192-page encyclical letter, mainly about global warming, also contains brief but scathing remarks on the digital filter we put on our human experience.</text><duplication>3.27868852459</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Pope prays before shroud of Turin</theme><text>Pope Francis plans to pray Sunday before the shroud of Turin, a piece of cloth that some believe is the burial wrapping of Jesus Christ.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Religious extremism looms over Myanmar</theme><text>The impact of Myanmar's repressive policy toward Rohingya Muslims was made clear in recent weeks with scenes of desperate people crammed into boats, an escalation of a miserable maritime flight in which an estimated 90,000 people have fallen prey to smugglers and traffickers since early 2014. The United Nations estimates that around 1,000 people have died on the way.</text><duplication>2.7027027027</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>What if ISIS seeks dirty bomb?</theme><text>Last week, the news emerged that ISIS terrorists have reportedly obtained radioactive materials from hospitals and research facilities captured in Iraq with a view to developing a radioactive "dirty bomb."</text><duplication>3.84615384615</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Sexual politics and the Mideast</theme><text>In a packed Cairo theater a couple of months ago, Ali Qandil brought down the house.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Is child marriage coming to an end?</theme><text>Today marks the Day of the African Child. This day was created by the African Union to commemorate a tragedy -- the massacre of hundreds of children in Soweto, South Africa who were demonstrating for the basic right to a decent education. Since then, the day has been used as an opportunity to focus a global spotlight on the injustices African children face, and on the actions we all need to take to ensure they can realize their rights.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Drone victims' family seeks justice</theme><text>In April this year, in the wake of the deaths of an American, Warren Weinstein, and an Italian, Giovanni Lo Porto, in a U.S. counterterrorism operation, U.S. President Barack Obama made an historic announcement, in which he said the following: "I take full responsibility for all our counterterrorism operations, including the one that inadvertently took the lives of Warren and Giovanni.</text><duplication>2.63157894737</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>How FIFA hid a most pernicious evil</theme><text>If you think FIFA is all about sport, you're missing the most important and potentially transformative campaign to uncover and punish the misdeeds of people who use soccer as a way to enrich themselves and their friends.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Orange: The new black in Bangladesh?</theme><text>When he first arrived in Bangladesh, photographer Ernst Coppejans saw it everywhere: men who had dyed their hair or their facial hair orange.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>New Zealand's most notorious gang: The Mongrel Mob</theme><text>A look at Jono Rotman's photos of bikers from New Zealand's Mighty Mongrel Mob, which is known for covering their faces with tattoos.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Spray paint, but without the street art</theme><text>It's spray paint but not as you know it -- while street art may have risen in popularity, the works on display are the polar opposite.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Plane spotting at Le Bourget Airshow 2015</theme><text>The 2015 Le Bourget Airshow is underway near Paris, filling the skies with some of the world's most impressive aircraft. The gallery above highlights of what is regarded as one of the aviation industry's most prestigious events.</text><duplication>9.75609756098</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Look at me! 26 selfies of the week</theme><text>Take a look at 26 selfies of the week from June 9 through June 16.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>The week in 39 photos</theme><text>Take a look at 39 photos of the week from June 4 through June 11.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Abandoned Chinese village swallowed by vines</theme><text>Ferns, weeds, and vines have completely covered this once bustling island town in China.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>What a shot! 41 amazing sports photos</theme><text>Take a look at 41 amazing sports photos from June 9 through June 15.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>The Annie Leibovitz of the Victorian era</theme><text>At a time when photography was still an evolving art form and dominated by men, Julia Margaret Cameron was taking stunning pictures of some of the 19th century's most notable personalities.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Classic paintings reimagined into urban settings</theme><text>Ukrainian artist Alexey Kondakov has photoshopped characters from mythology and antiquity into the modern day city. Browse through the gallery to see all the images.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Rare images of a 'rock star' mega-ship</theme><text>The Maersk Majestic is nearly as long as four NFL football fields. It's also taller than a 20-story building and too wide to pass through the Panama Canal.</text><duplication>4.44444444444</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>The Transformer superyacht that's also a jet</theme><text>As if superyachts weren't audacious and expensive enough already.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Paying a premium for England's green and pleasant lands</theme><text>The grounds of the Medmenham Abbey in Buckinghamshire, England, could easily be the set of a romanticized period drama.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>Fighting to win against the forces of nature</theme><text>Two CNN Heroes are among the earthquake survivors in Kathmandu, Nepal. And they are struggling in the aftermath.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>CNN.com - World</channel><theme>'It just went ballistic': Shark attacks teenager</theme><text>A shark attacked a teenager while he was spearfishing near a popular Australian beach. CNN affiliate Seven Network reports.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>France says Iran deal 'still not clear' as deadline nears</theme><text>JERUSALEM (Reuters) - France's Foreign Minister Laurent Fabius said on Sunday it was unclear whether an international deal could be reached on Iran's nuclear program by a June 30 deadline.</text><duplication>7.69230769231</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Al Jazeera says its journalist Ahmed Mansour to remain in custody in Germany</theme><text>CAIRO (Reuters) - The pan-Arab television network Al Jazeera said on Sunday that one of its best known journalists, Ahmed Mansour, had been ordered to remain in custody after appearing before a judge in Germany.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>British business leaders plan campaign for EU exit</theme><text>LONDON (Reuters) - A group of British business leaders and entrepreneurs are preparing to launch a campaign for Britain to leave the European Union at a planned membership referendum, a major donor to the UK Independence Party said.</text><duplication>4.08163265306</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Nigeria's Buhari advised to end fuel subsidy: sources</theme><text>ABUJA (Reuters) - Nigeria's new president, Muhammadu Buhari, has been advised by his transition committee to end a fuel subsidy program and privatize Nigeria's four refineries, senior sources in his party told Reuters on Sunday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Pope prays at Turin Shroud but skirts authenticity debate</theme><text>TURIN, Italy (Reuters) - Pope Francis prayed on Sunday before the mysterious shroud some Christians believe is Jesus's burial cloth but skirted the issue of its authenticity, saying it should remind people of all suffering and persecution.</text><duplication>4.0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Erdogan warns of risks, new poll if Turkey govt coalition delayed</theme><text>ISTANBUL (Reuters) - Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan on Sunday cited instability among neighboring states to urge political parties to form a coalition government quickly, or face the prospect of holding another election.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Palestinian shot after stabbing Israeli policeman in Jerusalem</theme><text>JERUSALEM (Reuters) - A Palestinian stabbed an Israeli paramilitary policeman at the entrance to the walled old city of Jerusalem on Sunday and was then shot by the policeman, police said.</text><duplication>11.4285714286</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>U.S., allies target Islamic State with 18 air strikes in Iraq</theme><text>WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. and coalition forces launched 18 air strikes against Islamic State targets in Iraq on Saturday, with four each in Tal Afar and Mosul, the U.S. military said in a statement.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Air strikes kill 15 in Yemen attacks: Houthi media</theme><text>SANAA (Reuters) - Arab air strikes killed 15 people and wounded dozens across Yemen late on Saturday, the Houthi-run Saba news agency reported.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Islamic State militants plant mines and bombs in Palmyra: monitoring group</theme><text>BEIRUT (Reuters) - Islamic State has planted mines and bombs in the ancient part of the central Syrian city of Palmyra, home to Roman-era ruins, a group monitoring the war said on Sunday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>South Africa opposition calls for investigation into Bashir's flight out</theme><text>JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - South Africa's main opposition on Sunday called for a full investigation into the government's failure to arrest Sudanese president Omar al-Bashir, who is due to face charges of genocide at the International Criminal Court.</text><duplication>5.0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>New South Africa mine union boss decries 'apartheid' wage system</theme><text>WESTONARIA, South Africa (Reuters) - The newly elected head of South Africa's biggest mine union said on Sunday that his members were still being paid "apartheid" wages, signaling a hard line ahead of gold sector wage talks due to start on Monday.</text><duplication>4.44444444444</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Two Ukrainian servicemen killed in past 24 hours: Ukraine military</theme><text>KIEV (Reuters) - Two Ukrainian servicemen have been killed and six wounded in the past 24 hours in separatist eastern territories, the Ukrainian military said on Sunday, describing an increase in fighting near the strategic port city of Mariupol.</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Britain extends commitment to NATO reassurance in Eastern Europe</theme><text>LONDON (Reuters) - Britain will boost its commitment to NATO reassurance efforts in Eastern Europe by extending the length of time its troops and fighter jets are involved, Defense Minister Michael Fallon said on Sunday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Amid fears of Greek controls, Cyprus shows restrictions are bearable</theme><text>NICOSIA (Reuters) - As Cyprus's financial system imploded in the spring of 2013, the island's leaders were given an ultimatum: sign up to a bailout deal or watch your banking system collapse.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Israel strike Lebanese remote area to destroy drone: Hezbollah TV</theme><text>BEIRUT (Reuters) - An Israeli war plane struck a remote area in Lebanon's western Bekaa region on Sunday to destroy a downed Israeli drone, al-Manar television, which is run by Hezbollah militant group, said.</text><duplication>43.4782608696</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Japan, South Korea hold talks amid 'comfort women' feud</theme><text>TOKYO (Reuters) - Japanese Foreign Minister Fumio Kishida held talks with his South Korean counterpart on Sunday in a bid to mend ties strained by a territorial dispute and a feud over "comfort women" forced to work in Japan's wartime military brothels.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Israeli PM takes aim at French peace initiative</theme><text>JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu prefaced talks about a French-led peace initiative on Sunday by saying foreign powers were trying to dictate to Israel a deal with the Palestinians.</text><duplication>5.6338028169</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Japan, South Korea hold talks amid 'comfort women' feud</theme><text>TOKYO (Reuters) - Japanese Foreign Minister Fumio Kishida held talks with his South Korean counterpart on Sunday in a bid to mend ties strained by a territorial dispute and a feud over "comfort women" forced to work in Japan's wartime military brothels.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Reuters: World News</channel><theme>Modi seeks to turn yoga record on its head as India stretches soft power</theme><text>NEW DELHI (Reuters) - Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi led tens of thousands of people in a yoga session in the center of the capital on Sunday to showcase the country's signature cultural export, which has prompted criticism of fomenting social divisions at home.</text><duplication>12.5</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Albania holds local polls, key to launch EU membership talks</theme><text>TIRANA, Albania (AP) &#8212; Albanians have started voting in local municipal elections, a key step in their efforts to launch membership negotiations with the European Union.</text><duplication>4.08163265306</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>40 Spanish experts rescue injured climber from deep cave</theme><text>MADRID (AP) &#8212; Emergency services in Spain's northeastern region of Catalonia say they have deployed 40 rescue experts to extricate an injured caver from deep underground.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Illicit drugs 'rampant' in California state prisons</theme><text>VACAVILLE, Calif. (AP) &#8212; California inmates are dying of drug overdoses at nearly triple the national rate and it's unclear whether the tough steps state officials took this year to stop illicit drugs from getting into prisons are having any effect, though they are prompting criticism from civil rights advocates.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>The Latest: Pan only player at US Open without a 3-putt</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; The latest from the U.S. Open (all times local):</text><duplication>6.45161290323</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Designer Todd Oldham to have solo exhibit at RISD museum</theme><text>PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) &#8212; An upcoming exhibit will focus on designer Todd Oldham's runway opus of the 1990s.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Pope: 'Powers' did nil when Jews were taken to Auschwitz</theme><text>TURIN, Italy (AP) &#8212; Pope Francis has denounced what he calls the "great powers" of the world for failing to act when there was intelligence indicating Jews, Christians, homosexuals and others were being transported to death camps in Europe during World War II.</text><duplication>93.9393939394</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>'Jurassic' holds box office, but 'Inside Out' shows bite</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; In a box-office bout of Tyrannosaurus-sized proportions, "Jurassic World" kept the No. 1 spot with one of the biggest second weeks ever, while Pixar's "Inside Out" nearly matched it.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Songs, prayer accompany 1st service at church since shooting</theme><text>CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) &#8212; Members of a historic black church will return to their sanctuary Sunday and worship, perhaps united like never before, and similar sermons of recovery and healing will reverberate throughout the country.</text><duplication>16.6666666667</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Latest on church shooting: Trayvon Martin's parents speak</theme><text>10:20 a.m.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>5 toughest performances in US Open history</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; Jason Day felt wobbly when he bent over and stood up, when he looked at his target and then back at his ball. One step at a time, he pushed himself around Chambers Bay in the third round of the U.S. Open until he had a 68 and a share of the lead.</text><duplication>3.125</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Nationals' Max Scherzer celebrates his no-hitter</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; A day later, Max Scherzer couldn't stop smiling.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>New Orleans police arrest suspect in killing of officer</theme><text>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#8212; Authorities canvassed a New Orleans neighborhood late into Saturday night in search of the man believed to have fatally shot a police officer who was transporting him &#8212; handcuffed and in the back of a police SUV &#8212; to jail.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Nevada to tax music events as Vegas becomes festival mecca</theme><text>LAS VEGAS (AP) &#8212; Northern Nevada has long been known as home to the freewheeling counterculture Burning Man festival in the starkly beautiful Black Rock Desert. In the past five years, Las Vegas, too, has evolved into a festival goers' mecca.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Couples, officials, foes readying for US gay marriage ruling</theme><text>CINCINNATI (AP) &#8212; With a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on same-sex marriage expected any day now, gay couples in states with bans are making wedding plans, courthouse officials are getting ready for different scenarios and steadfast foes are working on their strategies to keep up the opposition.</text><duplication>2.17391304348</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Romanian premier takes a month off citing health problems</theme><text>BUCHAREST, Romania (AP) &#8212; Romania's prime minister, who is under investigation for alleged corruption, says he will hand over his duties to a deputy for a month due to health problems.</text><duplication>90.9090909091</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>France warns of 'explosion' if no Mideast peace</theme><text>JERUSALEM (AP) &#8212; Israeli police say a Palestinian man has stabbed an Israeli paramilitary police officer, critically injuring him.</text><duplication>10.0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Manhunt for escaped killers shifts after possible sighting</theme><text>FRIENDSHIP, N.Y. (AP) &#8212; The search for two convicted killers in New York shifted after possible sightings in the southern part of the state, 350 miles from the prison where the men escaped two weeks ago.</text><duplication>4.34782608696</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Huckabee: Confederate battle flag should be up to state</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Republican Mike Huckabee says the Confederate flag debate in South Carolina is something for that state's residents to take on if they so choose, but he doesn't believe presidential candidates need to take a stand on the topic.</text><duplication>3.84615384615</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Illegal-dumping suspect nabbed at trash collection event</theme><text>KINGMAN, Ariz. (AP) &#8212; Arizona detectives holding a free trash collection event got more than just garbage. They also got their man.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Kanye West, Future perform at Birthday Bash 20 in Atlanta</theme><text>ATLANTA (AP) &#8212; Kanye West danced across the stage and knelt on his knees during a performance that left many repeating the words of his songs at one of Atlanta's most popular hip-hop concerts.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>European leaders working hard to keep Greece in eurozone</theme><text>ATHENS, Greece (AP) &#8212; A day ahead of a crucial emergency eurozone summit, Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras has presented a new proposal in calls to French President Francois Hollande, German Chancellor Angela Merkel and European Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Detained Al-Jazeera journalist to remain in German custody</theme><text>BERLIN (AP) &#8212; German prosecutors say they will be holding meetings about the case of a prominent Al-Jazeera journalist who was detained at a Berlin airport.</text><duplication>12.2448979592</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Not friends yet, but Japan and South Korea are talking</theme><text>TOKYO (AP) &#8212; Foreign ministers from Japan and South Korea held a rare meeting Sunday on the eve of the 50th anniversary since their countries normalized relations marred by Japan's colonization and World War II conquest.</text><duplication>84.2105263158</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Triple Crown stars still riding high 2 weeks after Belmont</theme><text>The party's still on for the first Triple Crown winner in 37 years &#8212; and the owner, trainer and jockey. Since American Pharoah completed his sweep of the Kentucky Derby, Preakness and Belmont Stakes, the past few weeks have turned into a whirlwind of TV appearances, first pitches and victory celebrations for owner Ahmed Zayat, trainer Bob Baffert and jockey Victor Espinoza.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Elegant comfort is on trend during Milan Fashion Week</theme><text>MILAN (AP) &#8212; Silky comfort is emerging as a trend on the second day of menswear previews for next spring and summer during Milan Fashion Week.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Iran lawmakers ban nuclear inspectors from military sites</theme><text>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) &#8212; Iran's parliament has voted to ban access to military sites and scientists as part of a future deal with world powers over its contested nuclear program.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Russian opposition activist attacked on campaign trip</theme><text>MOSCOW (AP) &#8212; A Russian activist who works with opposition leader Alexei Navalny has been hospitalized after being attacked while on a campaign trip in Russia's far east.</text><duplication>93.023255814</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Few clues in shooting at Detroit party that killed 1, hurt 9</theme><text>DETROIT (AP) &#8212; Detroit police say they have few leads in their investigation of a shooting at a block party that left one man dead and nine people wounded.</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Israel, Hamas in unspoken alliance against Gaza extremists</theme><text>KHAN YOUNIS, Gaza Strip (AP) &#8212; Nearly a year after a devastating war, Israel and Gaza's Hamas rulers appear to have formed an unspoken alliance in a common battle against the shared threat of jihadis aligned with the Islamic State group.</text><duplication>3.50877192982</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>In open letter, Swift criticizes 'shocking' Apple Music</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; In an open letter to Apple, Taylor Swift has criticized the company's new streaming music service for failing to pay artists for a free three-month trial.</text><duplication>13.9534883721</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Rosberg wins Austrian GP ahead of Mercedes teammate Hamilton</theme><text>SPEILBERG, Austria (AP) &#8212; Nico Rosberg showed his championship potential by overtaking pole sitter Lewis Hamilton on the first turn to win the Austrian Grand Prix in style on Sunday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Italian prosecutors seek to indict Bank of China, 297 people</theme><text>SHANGHAI (AP) &#8212; Italian prosecutors are seeking to indict 297 people and the Bank of China in connection with a massive money-laundering investigation reported by The Associated Press earlier this month.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Paris to help Mali put peace accord with Tuaregs in place</theme><text>PARIS (AP) &#8212; France's defense minister says that Paris will be helping Malians lock into place what he called a "historic" peace accord between northern Tuareg rebels and the government &#8212; which means a vast restructuring of the west African country's army.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Latest on church shooting: Charleston church bells ringing</theme><text>8:15 a.m.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>1 dead, 9 wounded in shooting at Detroit block party</theme><text>DETROIT (AP) &#8212; One person was killed and nine other wounded Saturday night when someone opened fire at a neighborhood block party on a basketball court in Detroit, police said.</text><duplication>27.9069767442</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Game of chicken over Greece risks slipping out of control</theme><text>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) &#8212; OK, guys. You can swerve now.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Question mark over Erdogan as Turk parties jockey for power</theme><text>ISTANBUL (AP) &#8212; Two weeks after Turkey's parliamentary elections, experts agree on one thing: No one really knows what's going to happen next.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>US developing 'Plan B' for deporting convicted plane bomber</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; The federal government has been exploring a "Plan B" to deport a man who placed a bomb on a Hawaii-bound airplane in 1982 and who has remained in immigration custody since being released from prison two years ago.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>State of fear: Survivors tell of life under IS rule</theme><text>ESKI MOSUL, Iraq (AP) &#8212; Inside the Islamic State's realm, the paper testifying that you have "repented" from your heretical past must be carried at all times. Many people laminate it just to be safe. It can mean the difference between life and death.</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>French minister takes stand against mobile telecom mergers</theme><text>PARIS (AP) &#8212; France's economy minister has come out strongly against consolidation in the country's mobile telecommunication industry after a media report claimed a merger is in the works between France's second-largest and fourth-largest operators.</text><duplication>4.08163265306</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Heading to Europe, Pentagon chief to boost military support</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Heading to Europe, Defense Secretary Ash Carter is carrying a strong message of U.S. military support for American allies and Baltic nations to help calm growing concerns about Russian aggression.</text><duplication>4.44444444444</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Pope pauses in silent prayer before Shroud of Turin</theme><text>TURIN, Italy (AP) &#8212; Pope Francis has paused in silent prayer before the Shroud of Turin on special display in the northern Italian city's cathedral.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Thousands at Stonehenge mark summer solstice</theme><text>LONDON (AP) &#8212; Thousands of revelers, new-agers and self-styled Druids descended on the ancient stone circle at Stonehenge, catching a brief glimpse of the sun as they marked the summer solstice &#8212; the longest day of the year in the northern hemisphere.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Austere brand of Islam on rise in Europe, stirring concerns</theme><text>PARIS (AP) &#8212; Its imams preach austere piety, its tenets demand strict separation of sexes &#8212; and some of its most radical adherents are heeding the call of jihad. Salafism, an Islamic movement based on a literal reading of the Quran, is on the rise in France, Germany and Britain, security officials say, with Salafis sharply increasing their influence in mosques and on the streets.</text><duplication>2.94117647059</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Somalia soldier, 4 militants killed in training site attack</theme><text>MOGADISHU, Somalia (AP) &#8212; A Somali police officer says four militants have been killed while trying to stage an attack on a training compound used for intelligence officials in Mogadishu.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>LEADING OFF: D'Arnaud and Sandoval hurting, Morton unbeaten</theme><text>A look at what's happening all around the major leagues today:</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Call for death penalty in shooting, but state lacks the drug</theme><text>COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) &#8212; Two days after the shooting deaths of nine people during a Bible study at a Charleston church, Republican Gov. Nikki Haley made a bold public statement: The gunman "absolutely" should be put to death. But her state, though largely pro-death penalty, can't secure one of the drugs needed for lethal injections and hasn't executed an inmate since 2011.</text><duplication>2.66666666667</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Kanye West, Future perform at Birthday Bash 20 in Atlanta</theme><text>ATLANTA (AP) &#8212; Kanye West danced across the stage and knelt on his knees during a performance that left many repeating the words of his songs at one of Atlanta's most popular hip-hop concerts.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Andre Ward beats Paul Smith in long-awaited return to ring</theme><text>OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) &#8212; Andre Ward made a triumphant return to the ring after a lengthy absence, delighting his home crowd by stopping England's Paul Smith in the ninth round Saturday night in a nontitle fight.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Virginia beats Florida 5-4, faces Vandy in CWS finals again</theme><text>OMAHA, Neb. (AP) &#8212; Kenny Towns drove in three runs, including the winner in the seventh, and Josh Sborz pitched four innings of shutout relief as Virginia defeated Florida 5-4 on Saturday night to set up a College World Series finals rematch against Vanderbilt.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Will Ferrell, Kristen Wiig in deadly dull 'Deadly Adoption'</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; The Lifetime movie that Will Ferrell and Kristen Wiig denied would ever happen aired Saturday night &#8212; and their denial is now easy to understand. It was lousy.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>An epic effort from Day for 4-way tie at US Open</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; One day after he collapsed from a bout of vertigo, Jason Day was standing tall at the U.S. Open.</text><duplication>5.26315789474</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Cousins killed in Berkeley balcony collapse had a twins bond</theme><text>COTATI, Calif. (AP) &#8212; Two cousins who were among the victims killed when a balcony collapsed will be mourned at a Northern California funeral and memorial service on Saturday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Italian prosecutors seek to indict Bank of China, 297 people</theme><text>ROME (AP) &#8212; Italian prosecutors are seeking to indict 297 people and the Bank of China in connection with a massive money-laundering investigation reported by The Associated Press earlier this month.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Day shoots 68, finishes at 4 under after 3rd round of Open</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; Australian Jason Day has teed off in the third round of the U.S. Open about 24 hours after collapsing at the end of his second round due to vertigo.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Latest on church shooting: Funeral set for Sen. Pinckney</theme><text>10:15 p.m.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Church shooting site to re-open; FBI reviews manifesto</theme><text>CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) &#8212; Felecia Sanders survived the attack on her Bible study group by pretending to be dead, but lost her son Tywanza.</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>The Latest: Spieth among leaders for final round of US Open</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; The latest from the U.S. Open (all times local):</text><duplication>6.45161290323</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Report: Wait lists for vets even longer today than last year</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; The number of veterans seeking health care but ending up on waiting lists of one month or more is 50 percent higher now than it was a year ago when a scandal over false records and long wait times wracked the Department of Veterans Affairs, The New York Times reported.</text><duplication>2.17391304348</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Police check out new lead on escaped New York prisoners</theme><text>LINDLEY, N.Y. (AP) &#8212; New York State Police are investigating a possible sighting of the two convicted killers who escaped from an upstate New York prison two weeks ago.</text><duplication>18.6046511628</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>New Orleans police officer killed while transporting suspect</theme><text>NEW ORLEANS (AP) &#8212; A handcuffed prisoner in a moving police cruiser somehow managed to grab a gun, fatally shoot the officer at the wheel and escape from the vehicle, which careened into a utility pole at a busy intersection, police said Saturday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Sweet Briar College to Remain Open</theme><text>Virginia attorney general announces rescue plan to keep all-female Sweet Briar College open.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Scherzer loses perfect game in 9th, throws no-hitter vs Bucs</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Just one strike from a perfect game, Max Scherzer saw it slip away with a misplaced slider. Or, some thought, a misplaced elbow.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Scherzer pitches no-hitter after losing perfect game in 9th</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Max Scherzer pitched a no-hitter Saturday, losing his perfect game with two outs in the ninth inning when he hit a batter in the Washington Nationals' 6-0 win over the Pittsburgh Pirates.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Confederate flag sets off debate in GOP 2016 class</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Former Massachusetts Gov. Mitt Romney called for the immediate removal of the Confederate battle flag from outside the South Carolina Statehouse, scrambling the 2016 Republican presidential contenders into staking a position on a contentious cultural issue.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Alaska island dog mysteriously crosses water to mainland</theme><text>KETCHIKAN, Alaska (AP) &#8212; Ed and Renee Schofield were surprised when they got a call from the pound in Ketchikan.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Not friends yet: Japan, S. Korea mark 50-year treaty</theme><text>TOKYO (AP) &#8212; Foreign ministers from Japan and South Korea are holding a rare meeting Sunday on the eve of the 50th anniversary since their countries normalized relations marred by Japan's colonization and World War II conquest.</text><duplication>72.4137931034</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Anthem proposes to buy Cigna for $184 per share</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; After getting the cold shoulder, U.S. health insurer Anthem Inc. said it's raising its offer to buy rival Cigna Corp. for $54 billion, including debt.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Tim Robbins takes in Emporio Armani as Fashion Week opens</theme><text>MILAN (AP) &#8212; Italy's fashion capital is getting a little more traffic than usual as Milan Fashion Week kicks off, thanks to the Expo 2015 world's fair at the city's gates, now in its second month.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Nationals' Scherzer pitching perfect game thru 8 vs Pirates</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Nationals ace Max Scherzer is pitching a perfect game through six innings against the Pittsburgh Pirates at Nationals Park.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Mermaids, aquatic creatures turn out for Coney Island parade</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; Tens of thousands of revelers turned out Saturday for Coney Island's 33rd annual Mermaid Parade despite gray skies and steady drizzle.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>WikiLeaks reveals Saudi intrigue and unpaid limo bills</theme><text>ISTANBUL (AP) &#8212; At the Saudi Embassy in Tehran, diplomats talk about kicking up trouble among disenchanted youth using Facebook and Twitter. At the embassy in Khartoum, they report on Iran's military aid to Sudan.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Sunni tribes, abandoned by Iraq, key to Islamic State fight</theme><text>HABANIYAH, Iraq (AP) &#8212; Parading across a desert base, hundreds of Sunni tribesmen who graduated a crash-training course stood ready to take on the Islamic State group on behalf of a government that many believed left them to die at the hands of the extremists.</text><duplication>3.44827586207</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Tuareg rebel group signs peace deal with Mali government</theme><text>BAMAKO, Mali (AP) &#8212; Mali's main coalition of Tuareg separatist rebels has signed a peace agreement with the government more than a month after other armed groups did so.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Man runs car into crowd in Austria, killing 3, injuring 34</theme><text>BERLIN (AP) &#8212; Austrian media say a man drove his van into a crowd in downtown Graz, killing two persons and injuring several people.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Obama spending Father's Day weekend at golf destination</theme><text>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) &#8212; With his wife and daughters away in Europe, President Barack Obama is spending Father's Day weekend in one of his favorite golf vacation destinations.</text><duplication>5.55555555556</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Religion and politics: GOP hopefuls' new insight on faith</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; The 2016 Republican presidential hopefuls are offering new insight into how faith would guide their decisions in the White House.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Teammate saves fellow serviceman after his parachute fails</theme><text>LONDON (AP) &#8212; A British military stunt team member whose chute failed to open properly owes a big thank you to a teammate who grabbed his parachute and got them both to a safe landing.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Spain: Tears in Barcelona at funeral for Germanwings victim</theme><text>MONTCADA, Spain (AP) &#8212; Three months after the Germanwings jet crashed in the French Alps, hundreds of tearful mourners have packed a funeral home to say goodbye to Robert Oliver Calvo &#8212; a passenger who died while on a business trip.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Angelina Jolie: We're living in era of 'mass displacement'</theme><text>MARDIN, Turkey (AP) &#8212; Actress Angelina Jolie is visiting a refugee camp in Mardin in southeastern Turkey as part of her work as special envoy for the United Nations High Commissioner on Refugees Antonio Guterres.</text><duplication>3.44827586207</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Potential top pick Karl-Anthony Towns works out for Wolves</theme><text>MINNEAPOLIS (AP) &#8212; Kentucky big man Karl-Anthony Towns worked out for the Minnesota Timberwolves on Saturday, less than a week before the Wolves pick first in the NBA draft.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Nationals' Harper back in lineup Saturday after leg injury</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Nationals right fielder Bryce Harper is back in Washington's lineup two days after suffering a mild left-hamstring strain, but remains under close watch by his coaching staff.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Islamic State-claimed car bombing kills 2 in Yemen's capital</theme><text>SANAA, Yemen (AP) &#8212; A car bomb exploded in front of a mosque in the capital Sanaa Saturday afternoon, killing at least two people and wounding six others, security officials said.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Clinton calls for 'common-sense' gun control, decries racism</theme><text>WASHINGTON (AP) &#8212; Hillary Rodham Clinton is calling for "common sense" gun control legislation and decrying "institutional racism" just days after a violent shooting in a historic South Carolina church that killed nine of its black members.</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Greek officials meet, prepare proposals for Eurozone summit</theme><text>ATHENS, Greece (AP) &#8212; Two days before a crucial summit of Eurozone leaders, Greek ministers are huddling to discuss strategy and assemble a new package of proposals, officials say.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>US Senator McCain slams European stance on Ukraine</theme><text>KIEV, Ukraine (AP) &#8212; U.S. Sen. John McCain has said during a visit to Ukraine that it is shameful that Washington's European allies have not done more to assist Ukrainian forces in their quest to defeat Russian-backed separatists in the east.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>'You are welcome:' The night Emanuel opened its door to evil</theme><text>CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) &#8212; When Angela Brown saw the Facebook post about a shooting at Emanuel African Methodist Episcopal Church, her mind immediately leapt to her aunt. Whenever the doors to Emanuel were open to its flock, Ethel Lance was there.</text><duplication>11.7647058824</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Workers clean up oil spill on California beaches by hand</theme><text>GOLETA, Calif. (AP) &#8212; Along a stretch of beach heavily marred by a crude oil spill, workers in hard hats and white protective suits use wire brushes and putty knives to scrape the black liquid off cobblestones and cliff faces.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>A US Open of birdies, bogeys and mind games at Chambers Bay</theme><text>UNIVERSITY PLACE, Wash. (AP) &#8212; Phil Mickelson staggered off Chambers Bay after a 74 that put a big dent in his chances to finally win a U.S. Open. He was eight shots behind and had little hope but to hit the gas in a major where neutral is often the best gear.</text><duplication>2.0618556701</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Man accused of church killings spoke of attacking college</theme><text>COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) &#8212; A black drinking buddy of the white man accused of killing nine people at a Charleston, South Carolina, church says that a week before the attack, the suspect announced plans to shoot up a college campus.</text><duplication>3.84615384615</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>'Boyhood' director Linklater loses appeal over film mementos</theme><text>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) &#8212; "Boyhood" director Richard Linklater again has lost in a lawsuit against his insurance company over what he says was $500,000 in property and film memorabilia destroyed by Texas wildfires in 2011.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Roadside bomb kills at least 12 civilians in Afghanistan</theme><text>KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) &#8212; Police say a powerful roadside bomb has exploded in southern Afghanistan, killing at least 12 civilians.</text><duplication>5.88235294118</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Newtown teens find healing in disaster relief service</theme><text>NEWTOWN, Conn. (AP) &#8212; Seven months after a gunman killed 26 people inside Sandy Hook Elementary School, an organization formed to help Newtown's children deal with the tragedy took 19 teenagers to Oklahoma, where they assisted in the cleanup from a series of devastating tornados.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>60 pizza-makers create nearly mile-long 'pie' in Milan</theme><text>ROME (AP) &#8212; The wait was on the long side for the pizza -- 18 hours -- but this was an extraordinary pie: 1.59545 kilometers, or nearly a mile long.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Kim Kardashian's spot on public radio show angers listeners</theme><text>CHICAGO (AP) &#8212; An appearance by Kim Kardashian on the National Public Radio show "Wait Wait ... Don't Tell Me!" has angered among some listeners.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>State of fear: Survivors tell of life under IS rule</theme><text>ESKI MOSUL, Iraq (AP) &#8212; When the Islamic State fighters burst into the Iraqi village of Eski Mosul, Sheikh Abdullah Ibrahim knew his wife was in trouble.</text><duplication>4.6511627907</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Texas turns away from criminal truancy courts for students</theme><text>DALLAS (AP) &#8212; A long-standing Texas law that has sent about 100,000 students a year to criminal court &#8212; and some to jail &#8212; for missing school is off the books, though a Justice Department investigation into one county's truancy courts continues.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Winners and losers from the E3 video-game show</theme><text>LOS ANGELES (AP) &#8212; The video-game industry's annual Electronic Entertainment Expo, which occupied the Los Angeles Convention Center this past week, was an overwhelming, exhausting experience &#8212; so many games, so little time. But most of the attendees had a similar reaction: "This is really fun." Still, some companies came off better than others. So who won E3?</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>A newsman gone astray will return to NBC seeking redemption</theme><text>NEW YORK (AP) &#8212; In 1974, CBS News anchor Walter Cronkite made a cameo appearance as himself on "The Mary Tyler Moore Show."</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>U.S. News - News</channel><theme>Portugal pilots warned of 70,000 homing pigeons</theme><text>LISBON, Portugal (AP) &#8212; Airplane pilots in Portugal have been advised to fly with special care after 70,000 homing pigeons were released in Spain to participate in a race back to their homes in Portugal.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Greece and EU 'insane not to do deal'</theme><text>The head of Greece's biggest bank tells the BBC it would be "insane" for Athens and the EU not to reach a deal at crunch talks.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>IS fighters 'laying mines in Palmyra'</theme><text>Activists say Islamic State fighters in Syria are planting bombs in Palmyra, an ancient city that has some of the Middle East's most important ruins.</text><duplication>9.3023255814</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Charleston pays tribute to victims</theme><text>The names of nine parishioners shot dead at an African-American church in South Carolina are read out in the church's first service since the attack.</text><duplication>5.26315789474</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Missing US prisoners 'spotted'</theme><text>Police launch a major search operation after a reported sighting of two convicted killers who escaped from a prison in New York state.</text><duplication>18.6046511628</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Pope Francis visits Turin Shroud</theme><text>Pope Francis pauses in silent prayer for several minutes before the Turin Shroud as part of special display.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>India PM leads yoga day celebration</theme><text>Thousands take part in a mass yoga programme in the Indian capital, Delhi, on the first ever International Yoga Day.</text><duplication>12.9032258065</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Al-Shabab launch Mogadishu attack</theme><text>At least three die as Somali jihadist group al-Shabab launches an attack on intelligence headquarters in the capital, Mogadishu.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Afghans counter Taliban offensive</theme><text>Government forces in northern Afghanistan launch a counter-offensive against the Taliban after they took control of a key district.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Italy seeks 300 over China 'fraud'</theme><text>Italian prosecutors want to indict the Bank of China's Milan branch and almost 300 people over a money-laundering scheme.</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Belgium unblocks Russian accounts</theme><text>Russian state accounts frozen by Belgium in a move condemned by Moscow have been unblocked, Belgium's foreign minister says</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Hill, 16, sets 100m youth record</theme><text>Sixteen-year-old Candace Hill runs a time that would have seen her finish seventh in the women's 100m at the 2012 Olympics.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Swift pulls album from Apple Music</theme><text>Taylor Swift writes open letter to Apple, explaining why she is pulling her hit album 1989 from its new streaming music service.</text><duplication>13.9534883721</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>California surfers break record</theme><text>Surfers in California break the world record for the most people riding a wave on a surfboard at the same time.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Galapagos tortoise put down in US</theme><text>A 150-year old Galapagos tortoise has been put down in California after suffering from arthritis and numerous other ailments.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>American novelist James Salter dies</theme><text>James Salter, an American author who was dubbed the "greatest writer you've never read," dies at the age of 90, according to his publisher.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Google cracks down on revenge porn</theme><text>The company says it's going to allow victims to request for certain images to be taken off search results.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Lone protester ends Guatemala march</theme><text>A lone protester in Guatemala receives a hero's welcome after covering more than 200 km (125 miles) in a protest against corruption.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Messi 'sorry' Neymar misses Copa</theme><text>Argentina captain Lionel Messi is "sorry" banned Brazil forward and Barcelona team-mate Neymar will miss the Copa America.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Mali's Tuareg rebels sign peace deal</theme><text>Rebels in Mali sign a peace deal with the government that will give partial autonomy to the north of the country.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Burundi grenade attacks hurt police</theme><text>Security officials say 11 policemen were injured in overnight grenade attacks in the capital Bujumbura amid continuing political unrest.</text><duplication>2.94117647059</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>India mourns alcohol poison deaths</theme><text>Residents of Mumbai mourn dozens killed by toxic alcohol in what police say is the worst incident of its kind in the Indian city in a decade.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Hundreds attack China police station</theme><text>Police in central China arrest 13 people after an attack on a police station in Hunan province by hundreds of villagers.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>UK aid 'can help deter migrants'</theme><text>The UK overseas aid budget should be used as part of measures to tackle the root cause of mass migration, Defence Secretary Michael Fallon says.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Rosberg overtakes Hamilton to win</theme><text>Nico Rosberg overtakes Lewis Hamilton to win in Austria after a nasty-looking crash between Fernando Alonso and Kimi Raikkonen.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Germany arrests al-Jazeera reporter</theme><text>Qatar-owned TV news network al-Jazeera says one of its journalists has been arrested in Germany at the request of Egypt.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Police 'role in radicalising sisters'</theme><text>UK police were "complicit" in the radicalisation of three sisters thought to be in Syria with their nine children, lawyers for the families say.</text><duplication>4.54545454545</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Swimmers treated after chemical leak</theme><text>Some 30 people are treated by paramedics for breathing problems following a chemical leak at a holiday park swimming pool.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Murray wins fourth Queen's title</theme><text>Andy Murray beats Kevin Anderson to join the likes of John McEnroe and Boris Becker as a four-time Queen's Club champion.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Petrobras case nets top businessmen</theme><text>The head of two of Brazil's leading construction firms are arrested as part of a major investigation into corruption at state-owned oil giant Petrobras.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>US plans new lorry emission rules</theme><text>US regulators propose new plans to reduce emissions from lorries and vans by 24% by 2027 as part of President Obama's drive to cut pollution.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Russia fury at Belgium asset seizure</theme><text>Russia protests to Belgium over its seizure of Russian state assets, after a court ordered compensation for shareholders in the now-defunct Yukos oil firm.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Sweden U21 0-1 England U21</theme><text>Jesse Lingard's late goal boosts England's European Under-21 Championship knockout stage hopes as they defeat Sweden.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Day delights as four lead US Open</theme><text>Australia's Jason Day battles vertigo to join Jordan Spieth, Dustin Johnson and Branden Grace in a share of the US Open lead.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Missing tests easy - Lewis-Francis</theme><text>British sprinter Mark Lewis-Francis says missing drugs tests, as Mo Farah did before London 2012, can "very easily" happen.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Top Gear should keep 'sense of danger'</theme><text>The BBC's director general says he hopes Top Gear's "edge" and "sense of danger" will continue with Chris Evans hosting.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>BBC: '10 years left of licence fee'</theme><text>BBC director general Tony Hall says the licence fee has "got 10 years of life left in it" after MPs say it is "becoming harder to justify".</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>UK to protect artefacts in war zones</theme><text>A major international agreement designed to protect cultural treasures during military conflicts is to be finally ratified by the UK.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: Racial attacks 'modern day lynchings'</theme><text>Rev Waltrina Middleton, whose cousin was murdered in the Charleston shooting, says the attacks on black people in the US are "modern day lynchings".</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: China's brand new islands</theme><text>China has been building new islands in the South China Sea to the alarm of its neighbours.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: India yoga event attracts thousands</theme><text>Thousands attend a mass yoga session in the Indian capital, Delhi, to mark the first International Yoga Day.</text><duplication>8.69565217391</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: Moment Waterloo news reached Britain</theme><text>The moment news of Napoleon's defeat reached the shores of Britain in 1815 is being re-enacted, concluding a week of commemorations.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: 'Most people on a surfboard' record set</theme><text>A new world record has been set in California when 66 people rode on a huge surfboard at once.</text><duplication>5.71428571429</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: Robot stars on Berlin opera stage</theme><text>A small robot, the same size as an 8-year-old child, is the star of an opera performance at Berlin's Komische Oper.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: Stranded on the Italy-Austria border</theme><text>Refugees from Syria, and many other people who have migrated to Europe in search of a better life, have been left stuck at national borders across the continent.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>VIDEO: UK jihadist was al-Shabab cameraman</theme><text>A British man killed while fighting with Islamist militant group al-Shabab in Kenya was second in command of his unit and also played the role of cameraman, the BBC has learned.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>In pictures: World Yoga Day</theme><text>Bending and stretching around the globe for World Yoga Day</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>The shadowy figures passing through Europe</theme><text>The shady figures slipping across Europe's borders</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Can Spain save horses on Andalusia pilgrimage?</theme><text>Can Spain stop mistreatment on Andalusian pilgrimage?</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>Inside Tadmur: The worst prison in the world?</theme><text>Is this the world's worst prison?</text><duplication>12.5</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>In pictures: Africa's high coiffure</theme><text>Pictures of the high coiffure on the Ivorian catwalks</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>BBC News - World</channel><theme>The ice-cream maker of Gaza</theme><text>The ice cream parlour that survived war and missiles</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Palmyra: IS 'Lays Explosives' At Ancient Site</theme><text>The extremist group captured Palmyra, famed for its historic ruins and priceless antiquities, last month.</text><duplication>5.71428571429</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Charleston Church Re-Opens After Massacre</theme><text>Reverend Norvel Goff told churchgoers the devil "cannot take control of your people" and "cannot take control of your church".</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Palestinian Shot After Stabbing Israeli Officer</theme><text>A paramilitary police officer is stabbed in the neck near the entrance to the Old City of Jerusalem.</text><duplication>11.4285714286</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Greece Offers New Deal Ahead Of Crunch Meeting</theme><text>The country's exit from the EU "won't be positive for the Greeks or the Europeans", France's leader warns.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Al Jazeera Journalist Detained At Berlin Airport</theme><text>Ahmed Mansour, who has British nationality, is arrested on an Egyptian warrant, accused of committing "several crimes".</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Balcony Collapse Victims Flown Back To Ireland</theme><text>The repatriation comes as their grieving parents thank the Berkeley community and their children's friends for their support.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Taylor Swift Keeps 1989 Off Apple Music</theme><text>The singer slams Apple's decision not to pay music royalties for three months, saying: "We don't ask you for free iPhones."</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Taliban Launches Hotline For Defectors</theme><text>The militants aim to lure government workers as they push into Kunduz and try to stop the spread of Islamic State's influence.</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Forty Rescuers Try To Save Man Trapped In Cave</theme><text>A team of specialists have been unable to free the seriously injured man because of the narrow width of tunnels in Cuberes cave.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - Breaking international news and headlines | Sky News</channel><theme>Police Arrest Man Suspected Of Shooting Cop</theme><text>Travis Boys was being transported to jail when he managed to get his hands from behind his back to the front and grab a weapon.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>South Africa's de Klerk, who ended apartheid along with Mandela, opposes sanctions on Israel</theme><text>The former South African president who helped end apartheid says sanctions against Israel would be "counterproductive." F.W.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Women protest detentions outside Egypt's presidential palace</theme><text>Dozens of women held a vigil Sunday outside Egypt's presidential palace, challenging a law that restricts protests and calling for the release of thousands of prisoners detained for violating the controversial measure.</text><duplication>12.1212121212</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Man arrested after trans-Atlantic flight diverted</theme><text>Authorities have arrested a 42-year-old man for endangering the safety of a plane after a United Airlines flight from Rome to Chicago was forced to divert to Northern Ireland.nd.</text><duplication>97.7777777778</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Egypt names ambassador to Israel, nearly 3 years after it recalled its last over 2012 Gaza war</theme><text>Egypt has named a new ambassador to Israel nearly three years after it had recalled the last one at the outset of the 2012 Israeli offensive in Gaza.</text><duplication>6.06060606061</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Romanian premier probed for corruption takes a month off work citing health problems</theme><text>Romania's prime minister, who is under investigation for alleged corruption, says he will hand over his duties to a deputy for a month due to health problems.</text><duplication>90.9090909091</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Lawyers slam police for their handling of the case of 3 British sisters feared to be in Syria</theme><text>Lawyers representing the family of three British sisters who disappeared in the Middle East with their nine children have slammed the police, arguing the authorities were complicit in the grooming and radicalization of the women.</text><duplication>4.54545454545</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Pope: World 'powers' did nothing as Jews, gays, were taken to death camps during WWII</theme><text>Pope Francis has denounced what he calls the "great powers" of the world for failing to act when there was intelligence indicating Jews, Christians, homosexuals and others were being transported to death camps in Europe during World War II.</text><duplication>93.9393939394</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Women rally outside of Egypt's presidential palace over thousands detained on protest law</theme><text>Dozens of women have held a vigil outside Egypt's presidential palace, calling for the release of thousands detained for violating the country's controversial protest law.</text><duplication>14.2857142857</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Not friends yet, but Japan and South Korea are talking</theme><text>Foreign ministers from Japan and South Korea held a rare meeting Sunday on the eve of the 50th anniversary of their countries normalizing relations marred by Japan's colonization and World War II conquest.</text><duplication>84.2105263158</duplication></news><news><channel>FOX News</channel><theme>Russian opposition activist who works with Navalny hospitalized after attack on campaign trip</theme><text>A Russian activist who works with opposition leader Alexei Navalny has been hospitalized after being attacked while on a campaign trip in Russia's far east.</text><duplication>93.023255814</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Israel Bets On Recycled Water To Meet Its Growing Thirst</theme><text>Treated sewage water accounts for half the water used by Israel's farms. Entrepreneurs are experimenting with ways to cut costs and to ensure that the 86 percent of wastewater that's recycled is safe.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>For A British Man, Fighting ISIS Was Simply The Right Thing To Do</theme><text>Macer Gifford &#8212; an alias he uses to protect his family &#8212; left his job as a financial trader in London to fight ISIS in Syria. He lost much of what he had, but says he never regretted his decision.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>French Ecology Minister Calls For A Nutella Boycott</theme><text>She asked consumers to stop eating Nutella  because it's made with palm oil, which contributes to deforestation. NPR's Rachel Martin talks with Glenn Hurowitz, managing director of Climate Advisers.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>German Protesters Exhume Migrant Graves To Shock Europe Into Action</theme><text>Germans activists want Europe to accepting more of the millions fleeing the world's conflict zones. They're exhuming migrants from unmarked graves in Italy and reburying them in Berlin.</text><duplication>7.14285714286</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>35,000 Bend It With Modi As India Launches World Yoga Day</theme><text>Led by Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, tens of thousands of government officials, soldiers and students performed yoga in New Delhi Saturday for the first-ever International Day of Yoga.</text><duplication>21.0526315789</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Europe's Migrant Crisis Spreads Ashore As Refugees Enter Bulgaria On Foot</theme><text>Migrants from Syria and other nations are fleeing to Europe not just by sea but also over land via Turkey. In Bulgaria, one of the European Union's poorest nations, about 1,000 people used to cross the border in a year. Last weekend alone, 650 people tried to cross, most of them unsuccessfully.A version of this story originally aired on All Things Considered on June 17, 2015.</text><duplication>4.0404040404</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Prophet Muhammad Cartoons To Be Broadcast On Dutch TV</theme><text>A far-right politician who gave a speech at a Dallas area event attacked last month for featuring a Muhammad drawing contest, said the images will be aired on Wednesday.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Anti-Austerity Marchers Rally In London Calling For End To Cuts</theme><text>Tens of thousands turned out in the capital and other U.K. cities, vowing it was the start of a campaign to force the Conservative government to reverse deep spending cuts.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Greece Pledges New Proposal To Resolve Debt Crisis</theme><text>The European Central Bank gave Greece an emergency loan of more than $2 billion on Friday to stave off collapse, but a June 30 deadline looms for payment on the next installment of an IMF loan.</text><duplication>7.69230769231</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>At Waterloo Re-Enactment, History So Real You Can Taste It</theme><text>He may have lost, but Napoleon still holds a fascination for thousands of re-enactors who came to Belgium this week to eat, sleep and wage mock war in the manner of the 1815 battle of Waterloo.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Bin Laden Son Asked U.S. For Father's Death Certificate, Wikileaks Says</theme><text>The website has begun the release of 500,000 documents it says are related to Saudi Arabian diplomatic communications. Among them was the request from Abdullah bin Laden.</text><duplication>3.57142857143</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>South Korea, Thailand Report No New MERS Cases</theme><text>The number of cases in South Korea has remained steady at 166 for more than two weeks, but the death of a 63-year-old man brought to 25 the number of deaths from Middle East Respiratory Syndrome.</text><duplication>4.0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Barcelona's Mom-And-Pop Tapas Bars Take On The Big Tourist Chains</theme><text>Off the beaten tourist paths, neighborhood tapas bars are part of Spain's charm. But many are being forced out by rising rents. A tour group hopes to save them by helping travelers find them.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>Citing Abuse, Haitian Immigrants Flee Dominican Republic</theme><text>The deadline has passed for illegal immigrants in the Dominican Republic to begin the process to get regularized or to get out of the country. Authorities say most illegal immigrants will be deported.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World : NPR</channel><theme>How The Kurds Are Succeeding In Iraq</theme><text>Kurdish fighters have recaptured a strategic Syrian city from the so-called Islamic State. NPR's Scott Simon talks to Joshua Landis at the University of Oklahoma about the Kurds' strategy.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World News - UPI.com</channel><theme>10 dead in Mexico beer distribution center shoot-out</theme><text>Amy R. Connolly</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Gas Discoveries in the East Mediterranean</theme><text>Countries in the East Mediterranean can use gas discoveries as a catalyst for regional cooperation, unlocking the region's production potential.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Viewpoints: Iraq and Syria's Ongoing Conflagration</theme><text>Sectarian warfare in Iraq and a brutal regime in Syria have led to a level of violence and chaos that is extreme even by the Middle East's standards.</text><duplication>9.3023255814</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Mercosur and Pacific Alliance: Latin America Divided</theme><text>Two regional blocs have formed in Latin America that have come to highlight an ideological schism between left-leaning and right-leaning governments.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Saudi Arabia Continues to Turn Screws on U.S. Shale</theme><text>Saudi Arabia has succeeded in maintaining its market share throughout the oil bust by continuing to ratchet up production.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Food Insecurity and Climate Change in Egypt</theme><text>Egypt must adapt to climate change by introducing new crops, investing in farming technology and changing subsidies to protect the most vulnerable.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Bolivia Wrestles Chile for Ocean Access</theme><text>Bolivia lost its coastline in the War of the Pacific in the late 1800s, and ever since it has been battling Chile to regain the land and what lies beneath it.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Nicaragua: China's Canal in Latin America</theme><text>Nicaragua is moving forward on an Atlantic-Pacific canal that would dwarf the Panama Canal in capacity, and China has plenty to gain by backing the project.</text><duplication>4.44444444444</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Viewpoints: Netanyahu Further Isolates Israel</theme><text>Through his increasingly belligerent position toward Palestinians and Iran, Netanyahu has managed to incense the United States, Israel's one indispensable ally.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>World's 10 Biggest Energy Gluttons</theme><text>A look into which countries use the most energy per capita reveals some surprising results, from the Middle East to the Caribbean.</text><duplication>5.26315789474</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Overcoming ISIS: Transcending Sectarian Rivalries</theme><text>The Western strategy of fighting warfare with warfare has only perpetuated sectarian divides, creating the very environment that fostered ISIS.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Oil Prices Change the Face of Geopolitics</theme><text>The plunge in oil prices has had a significant effect on Russia, Iran and Venezuela, and is changing those countries' geopolitical calculus.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Norway's Oil Decline Accelerates</theme><text>With oil prices tumbling and new oil projects being scrapped, Norway may need to begin building a post-oil economy sooner than it thought.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Will Ukraine Commit Economic Suicide?</theme><text>Ukraine's crippling 55 percent tax on private gas producers threatens to damage the economy, scare off investors and decimate gas production.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>China's Asian Infrastructure Investment Bank</theme><text>The AIIB is a game changer for China in multilateral financial architecture. The Bank presents both a challenge and an opportunity for India.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Business Underpins India-U.S. Defense Deal</theme><text>In its recent defense technology deal with the U.S., India has laid the groundwork for creating a robust long-term defense industrial base.</text><duplication>6.45161290323</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Australia: Fanning the Flames of Warming and Warfare</theme><text>Australia is a case study for how the West prioritizes fossil fuels and military intervention over developing alternative energy and regional accord.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>No U.S. Military Bases: Latin America's Call for Sovereignty</theme><text>At this weekend's Summit of the Americas, Latin American nations continue to push back against U.S. dominance, starting with U.S. military bases.</text><duplication>4.44444444444</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Colombia: Prospects for Peace</theme><text>After 50 years of war, Colombia may finally be waking from its nightmare, but not everyone is pleased with negotiations between President Santos and the FARC.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Global Divestment Day: Shifting Investments to Clean Energy</theme><text>The divestment movement aims to combat climate change by stripping investments from fossil fuels and redirecting them toward renewable energy.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Renew the African Growth and Opportunity Act</theme><text>If revised and renewed, the AGOA would encourage growth and development in sub-Saharan Africa while also benefitting U.S. economic interests.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>Ebola: A Global Wake-Up Call</theme><text>The Ebola outbreak in West Africa is challenging the health systems of some very poor countries, and a proper response requires global cooperation.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Top Headlines from World Press Review</channel><theme>U.S.-Africa Summit: Partnership Opportunities</theme><text>The upcoming summit between U.S. and African leaders is likely to make progress on a number of investment, development and security issues.</text><duplication>4.54545454545</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Ex-Playmate drops Hefner bombshell</theme><text>BREKKIE WRAP: Fake sex parties, strict curfews and power games. Former Bunny Holly Madison has revealed the truth about Hugh Hefner&amp;#8217;s Playboy empire.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>&#8216;The devil was trying to take charge&#8217;</theme><text>FOUR days after a white supremacist gunned down nine black congregants, the Charleston church has reopened for an emotional service.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Is this the solution to stop people smoking?</theme><text>IN a measure to prevent young people from the health risks associated with cigarettes, Hawaii has raised the legal smoking age to 21.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Gunmen open fire on street parties</theme><text>GUNMEN have opened fire on picnics in Detroit and Philadelphia, killing one and injuring 16, including an 18-month-old baby.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>The past catches up with Cosby</theme><text>A FORMER Playboy Bunny who says legendary comedian Bill Cosby drugged and raped her has told her story in startling detail.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Can you spot the 50 landmarks?</theme><text>PERCHED high above the crowded streets lies one of the best views in the modern world. But can you spot the landmarks?</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Greek Aussies offer a helping hand</theme><text>THEY left Greece for a better life but now Australia&amp;#8217;s large Greek community is giving something back to their &amp;#8220;home&amp;#8221; in its dire hour of need.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Guards &#8216;filmed sex with refugees&#8217;</theme><text>AUSTRALIAN detention centre guards allegedly paid female refugees on Nauru for sex and circulated videos of the encounters, a former social worker claims.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>Has North Korea cured AIDS?</theme><text>NORTH KOREA says it has succeeded where the greatest minds in science have failed: Producing a single drug that can cure AIDS, MERS, SARS and ebola.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NEWS.com.au | World</channel><theme>&#8216;I knew where I was coming&#8217;: Aussie IS doctor</theme><text>THE Australian doctor working for the Islamic State in Syria has issued a defiant message via his Facebook page reinforcing how happy he is with the extremist group.</text><duplication>5.71428571429</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Millions in India, world mark 1st International Yoga Day</theme><text>Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi had lobbied the U.N. to declare June 21 as the global Yoga Day.</text><duplication>16.2162162162</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Marines looking at deploying aboard foreign ships</theme><text>Facing budget constraints the Marines looking to partner with foreign navies.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Man arrested after trans-Atlantic flight diverted</theme><text>Many passengers spent the night at the Belfast airport, because not enough hotel space.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Traffic light has been red for nearly 30 years</theme><text>When at light, drivers in Dresden, Germany can only turn right on red.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Voices: At last, a breakthrough for Turkey's Kurds</theme><text>After years of oppression, Kurds' success in Turkish election brings sense of hope</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Netanyahu gives cool reception to French peace initiative</theme><text>France has said it will propose a resolution in the United Nation Security Council with a framework for negotiations toward resolving the Israeli-Palestinian conflict.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Sunday is International Yoga Day: Learn to do it in 2 minutes</theme><text>In just two minutes, check out these moves that even dear old dad could master.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Raw: Anti-Austerity Protest in London</theme><text>Thousands of demonstrators marched through London to protest against British government austerity programs and spending cuts on Saturday. (June 20)</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Man runs car into crowd killing 3, injuring 34 in Austria</theme><text>Police said the driver had been arrested.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Good Samaritan may be sued for rescuing dog from train tracks</theme><text>A woman in Lima, Peru bravely stepped onto train tracks to rescue a dog. But because jumping onto the tracks is illegal, she could be fined or even sued. Mara Montalbano (@maramontalbano) has the story.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Russia appears to extend aid hand to Greece</theme><text>Russia considers financial aid for Greece as the cash-strapped nation runs out of time to resolve its debt crisis.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Taiwan becomes first Asian nation with Silicon Valley launch pad</theme><text>France, Germany, Switzerland, Sweden, Norway, Denmark, Finland and Iceland also have outposts.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Why is the US crushing 1 ton of Ivory in Times Square?</theme><text>The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service will crush one ton of ivory in Times Square to send a message to illegal wildlife poachers and traffickers.
Video provided by Newsy</text><duplication>23.2558139535</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Pope Francis lights up Twitter feed with climate change truth bombs</theme><text>Pope Francis didn't pull any punches in his letter on climate change.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Pope steers Church focus to climate change with encyclical</theme><text>Pope Francis released his first encyclical Thursday and in it the pontiff focuses on climate change and global inequality.
Video provided by Newsy</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Denmark Embassy honors Bill Clinton with a portrait</theme><text>In 1997, Bill Clinton made the first trip to Denmark for a sitting president.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Kurds savor victory over ISIL in Syria</theme><text>Despite victory, Kurds have no plans to move toward ISIL's stronghold in Raqqa, Syria.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Global warming deniers unimpressed with pope's climate encyclical</theme><text>The pope's encyclical on climate change Thursday was met with criticism by prominent climate deniers and skeptics.</text><duplication>3.27868852459</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Solar-powered plane could be stuck in Japan 'for months'</theme><text>Solar-powered plane now ready to fly but must wait out bad weather, perhaps for up to 2 months.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>The heat goes on: Warmest May, spring and year on record</theme><text>The Earth just had its warmest May, warmest spring, and warmest first five months (Jan-May) on record.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Argentina proposes catcalling fines</theme><text>Argentina is proposing fines as a way to punish people caught cat calling anyone on the street. Patrick Jones (@Patrick_E_Jones) discusses.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>France just ruined Nutella for everybody</theme><text>France's ecology minister says  products with palm oil lead to massive deforestation.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Analysis: Pope Francis spares few in tough-love demands to save planet</theme><text>The world's most popular figure demands top-down cultural reform to save the planet.</text><duplication>12.5</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>Read Pope Francis' climate encyclical</theme><text>Pope Francis issued his long-awaited encyclical on the environment Thursday.</text><duplication>10.0</duplication></news><news><channel>USATODAY - World Top Stories</channel><theme>U.N. refugee agency: World's displaced reach record high</theme><text>Last year, 126,800 refugees were able to return to their home countries.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Passengers on Trans-Atlantic Flight Sleep in Airport After Plane Diverted</theme><text>United Airlines flight from Rome to Chicago diverted due to unruly passenger.</text><duplication>20.6896551724</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Photos:  Powerful Photos Show Plight of Millions of Refugees</theme><text>On June 20, the world commemorates the strength, courage and resilience of millions of refugees.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Red Devils Parachutist Gets Tangled With Teammate in Mid-Air</theme><text>Organizers say parachutes opened but men became tangled together.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>How Muslims Observe Ramadan Where the Sun Never Sets</theme><text>For Muslims who live in the land of the "Midnight Sun," where the sun is still up at midnight or all day, Ramadan presents a unique challenge.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Baby Pygmy Hippo Makes His 1st Public Splash</theme><text>A pygmy hippopotamus calf has splashed into the water with his mom for the first time in front of viewers at the Melbourne Zoo in Australia.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Mystery Deepens With 'No Evidence' Linking Body to Plane Stowaway</theme><text>Police said there is no clear link between the building body and stowaway.</text><duplication>6.89655172414</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Terror Report: Attack Fatalities Have Spiked 81 Percent</theme><text>The number of terrorist attacks worldwide spiked by 81 percent in 2014, according to a new State Department report.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Possible Stowaway Incidents Eyed After Body Found</theme><text>Authorities are investigating whether two men stowed away on a British Airways flight from Johannesburg, South Africa, to London.</text><duplication>6.06060606061</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Baby Beckham Outfits Go on Sale</theme><text>Fashionistas lined outside a store today.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Aid Workers Describe Horrific Effects of Syria's Chlorine Warfare</theme><text>Lawmakers grappled Wednesday with gruesome new evidence provided by aid workers showing the effects of the Assad regime's use of chlorine gas against civilians.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>South Africa's De Klerk Opposes Sanctions on Israel</theme><text>South Africa's de Klerk, who ended apartheid along with Mandela, opposes sanctions on Israel</text><duplication>5.0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Women Protest Detentions Outside Egypt's Presidential Palace</theme><text>Women rally outside of Egypt's presidential palace over thousands detained on protest law</text><duplication>14.2857142857</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Egypt Names Ambassador to Israel After Nearly 3 Years</theme><text>Egypt names ambassador to Israel, nearly 3 years after it recalled its last over 2012 Gaza war</text><duplication>6.06060606061</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Romanian Premier Takes a Month off Citing Health Problems</theme><text>Romanian premier probed for corruption takes a month off work citing health problems</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Lawyers Slam Police in Missing British Sisters Case</theme><text>Lawyers slam police for their handling of the case of 3 British sisters feared to be in Syria</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>France Warns of 'Explosion' If No Mideast Peace</theme><text>French foreign minister warns of 'explosion' if Israeli-Palestinian stalemate goes on</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Man Arrested After Trans-Atlantic Flight Diverted</theme><text>Man arrested after flight from Rome to Chicago was diverted to Northern Ireland</text><duplication>13.7931034483</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>European Leaders Working Hard to Keep Greece in Eurozone</theme><text>European leaders say accord between Greece, creditors is possible ahead of Monday's summit</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Detained Al-Jazeera Journalist to Remain in German Custody</theme><text>Al-Jazeera journalist to remain in German custody; prosecutors to decide next week on his fate</text><duplication>11.1111111111</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Not Friends yet, but Japan and South Korea Are Talking</theme><text>Neighbors but not friends: Japan, South Korea ministers talk ahead of 50th anniversary of ties</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  Red Devils Parachutist Tangles With Teammate in Mid-Air</theme><text>Thousands of onlookers at the Whitehaven Airshow in the United Kingdom held their breath during the stunt.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  Watch One Ton of Ivory Get Crushed in Times Square</theme><text>The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service raised awareness on Friday about the illegal Ivory trade and urged the public not to buy such products.</text><duplication>23.2558139535</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  Judge Sets SC Shooter Bond at $1Million; California Fire Blazes On Close to Big Bear; Tiger Woods Loses His Grip</theme><text>Judge sets Dylann Roof bond at $1Million; Fire blazes on close to Big Bear, California, forcing hundreds to evacuate; Tiger Woods loses his grip during the US Open.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  SC Church Shooting Suspect Caught; Severe Flooding Across Midwest; 4-Year-Old Girl Giggles During Stunt-Plane Joyride</theme><text>South Carolina church shooting suspect Dylann Roof caught; severe flooding in Texas, Kansas, Oklahoma and Indiana; little girl giggles as pilot dad takes her on joyride in plane.</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  U.S. Attorney General Loretta Lynch Sworn In; Study Finds Water Resources Depleting Worldwide; Woman in Bali Gets Phone Stolen by Selfie Monkey</theme><text>United States Attorney General Loretta Lynch sworn in by Supreme Court Justice Sotomayor; Scientists worry about water resources depleting worldwide; Woman in Bali gets phone stolen by selfie monkey.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  Lynch Sworn In As Attorney General, Trump Hits The Campaign Trail, McIlroy Practices For The U.S. Open</theme><text>United States Attorney General Loretta Lynch sworn in by Supreme Court Justice Sotomayor; Scientists worry about water resources depleting worldwide; Woman in Bali gets phone stolen by selfie monkey.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  Fighting Terrorism With Flip Flops</theme><text>Former Army Ranger Matthew Griffin's business is creating jobs in war-torn countries.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Watch:  The Magna Carta Celebrates 800th Anniversary</theme><text>Members of the royal family celebrated the 800th anniversary of the Magna Carta, the legal document sealed by King John in 1215 that laid the groundwork for many of the rights still protected in today's democracies.</text><duplication>4.25531914894</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Full Episode:  WN 06/20/15: FBI Investigating Website Possibly Tied to Alleged Church Gunman</theme><text>New Leads In Search for Escaped New York Prisoners; 35 Million Under Threat of Severe Storms; Wildfires Burn Out of Control in Alaska, California.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Full Episode:  Nightline 06/19/15:  Charleston Church Massacre Victims' Families Confront Alleged Killer</theme><text>'The Wolfpack': Six Brothers With a Haunting Past; Military Dads Surprise Kids in Special Father's Day Reunion</text><duplication>5.55555555556</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Full Episode:  20/20 06/19/15:  'The Wolfpack'</theme><text>'Wolfpack' Brothers Grew Up Locked in NYC Apartment for Years; Chance Encounter With Filmmaker Changes 'Wolfpack' Brothers' Lives; Brothers Meet Grandma For First Time at 'Wolfpack' Family Reunion</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Full Episode:  GMA 06/19/15: License Plate, Haircut Helped Hero Florist Spot Dylann Roof</theme><text>Watch Surprise Father's Day Reunion With Deployed Dads; Superstar Adam Lambert Performs Live in Central Park.</text><duplication>5.55555555556</duplication></news><news><channel>ABC News: International</channel><theme>Full Episode:  This Week 06/14/15: Chris Christie Takes On Clinton's NYC Speech</theme><text>Guests: Chris Christie, Joel Benenson, Thomas Perez, Katrina vanden Heuvel, Bill Kristol, Ana Navarro, Neera Tanden</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Al-Jazeera journalist detained in Germany says charges were 'fabricated' - video</theme><text>Ahmed Mansour, a prominent al-Jazeera Arabic journalist, speaks out about being detained in Germany over an Egyptian arrest warrant. Mansour was detained on Saturday while trying to board a Qatar Airways flight at Berlin's Tegel airport heading to Doha, according to al-Jazeera. Mansour says the charges against him were 'fabricated' </text><duplication>7.69230769231</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Three sisters, nine children, one dangerous journey to the heart of Isis. What is the lure of the caliphate?</theme><text>Hundreds of Britons have joined the Islamist militants. Hassan Hassan has interviewed dozens of members of the group in Syria and Iraq</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>&#8216;Even if your home town is Dewsbury, you can be British and Muslim at the same time&#8217;</theme><text>The West Yorkshire town has a reputation as a hotbed of Islamic extremism, thanks to 7/7 mastermind Mohammad Siddique Khan and the 17-year-old suicide bomber Talha Asmal. Its inhabitants say they deserve better</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Goodbye, Lenin: how a weighty symbol of the Soviet past divided a Ukrainian city</theme><text>Bitter arguments among local councillors and citizens over the fate of the communist hero&#8217;s statue highlighted a deep generational rift</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>It&#8217;s not about where we put a runway. Don&#8217;t build one at all | letters</theme><text>Introduce a polluters&#8217; tax on frequent flyers</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>South Carolina protest calls for removal of Confederate flag - video</theme><text>Thousands protest in South Carolina's capital on Saturday against the Confederate flag that flies on the state house grounds, an issue reignited by the shooting of nine black churchgoers in Charleston. The flag of the Confederacy has fluttered near the state legislature in Columbia since the early 1960s when it was put up during the peak of the civil rights movement </text><duplication>3.1746031746</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Austerity protest: thousands take to streets of London to demonstrate against welfare cuts - video</theme><text>Thousands of anti-austerity protesters demonstrate in London's financial district on Saturday against the government's plans for public spending cuts. Speeches were held outside the Bank of England before protesters made their way towards the Houses of Parliament. Many are angered at the potential cuts which will affect vulnerable groups, such as people with disabilities. One protester says, 'I just don't think the poor should have to suffer for the mistakes of the rich' </text><duplication>2.22222222222</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Rick Perry describes Charleston church shooting as an 'accident' - video</theme><text>Republican presidential candidate Rick Perry suggests on Friday that the fatal shooting at Emanuel AME church in Charleston, South Carolina, was an 'accident'. The former Texas governor was asked about the shooting, in which nine black people were killed by a white male, during an interview with the conservative NewsmaxTV. A spokesman for Perry later clarified that he had meant to say 'incident'</text><duplication>2.85714285714</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Vicar equates homosexuality to paedophilia and adultery - audio</theme><text>The Rev Melvin Tinker, vicar of St John in Newland in Hull, says on Minster FM that he is outraged to hear that Canon Michael Smith of York Minster would be giving a blessing to York Pride on Saturday. Tinker is repeatedly asked by an interviewer if he is likening homosexuality to paedophilia. Tinker says that if homosexual sex falls into the immoral category, then it is in the same category as any other immoral action</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Charleston shooting: sense of urgency needed over gun control, says Obama - video</theme><text>US president Barack Obama discusses the shooting at the Emanuel AME church in Charleston, while addressing the US conference of mayors in San Francisco on Friday. Obama says he is not resigned to the challenge of tackling the problem of gun control in the US. He says 'I have faith that we will eventually do the right thing ... [but] we have to feel a sense of urgency.' Gun advocacy groups including the National Rifle Association have said a new national debate over guns was inappropriate so soon after the massacre </text><duplication>2.04081632653</duplication></news><news><channel>World news | The Guardian</channel><theme>Dylann Roof appears in court accused of Charleston shooting - video</theme><text>Dylann Roof, 21, stood quietly through the hearing, providing brief answers to the judge's questions, confirming his name and address and saying he was unemployed before family members of several of the nine worshippers he is alleged to have shot dead at the nearly-200-year-old Emanuel African Methodist Episcopal church spoke. Some said they forgave Roof. </text><duplication>9.09090909091</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Charleston massacre church reopens in triumph over 'the Devil'</theme><text>Hundreds of people at Emanuel African Methodist Episcopal Church in Charleston as it reopens to worshippers days after gunman shot dead nine church members</text><duplication>11.7647058824</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>'Queen Angela' looks forward to meeting Queen Elizabeth on state visit</theme><text>Two of Europe's most-powerful woman to hold private meeting in Berlin, as Germany's Angela Merkel hailed the British monarch for overseeing better relations</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Afghan Taliban offer government workers 'hotline' number to defect</theme><text>The move demonstrates the Taliban's efforts to boost public support following a string of defections to Islamic State in recent months</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Isil lay mines in Syria's ancient Palmyra ruins</theme><text>Islamic State militants have laid landmines and explosives around the Unesco heritage site of Palmyra, say observation group</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Yoga at the Eiffel Tower</theme><text>At least 1,500 people take part in yoga at the Eiffel Tower in Paris to celebrate the first ever International Day of Yoga</text><duplication>21.0526315789</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Johnny Depp sells French estate - including pirate-themed room - for &#163;16.5 million</theme><text>The Pirates of the Caribbean star wants to "move on" by selling the 200-year-old French village he bought as a holiday home and and spent years lovingly restoring</text><duplication>2.7027027027</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Thousands of dogs and cats slaughtered at China festival despite government promises to crack down</theme><text>Sellers kept the dogs dozens to a cage before electrocuting and skinned them alive, before serving them with lychee</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Israel conducts air strike over the border in Lebanon to destroy its own downed drone</theme><text>Israeli war plane struck a remote area in Lebanon's western Bekaa region to destroy a drone which landed over the border</text><duplication>43.4782608696</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Bosnian 'with history of beating wife' accused of ploughing car into Austria crowd</theme><text>Alen Rizvanovi?, a father of two whose wife had just left him, is accused of killing a newlywed, a four-year-old boy and a cyclist, when he ploughed his car into a busy shopping street</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Modi turns yogi as millions celebrate International Yoga Day</theme><text>Serene scenes as the sun rises on India's bid to set a new world yoga record, an event that has put community relations through strenuous contortions</text><duplication>5.71428571429</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Pope Francis prays at mysterious Turin Shroud</theme><text>Pope Francis prays before the mysterious Shroud of Turin, believed by Christians to be the burial cloth of Jesus but held by sceptics to be a medieval fake</text><duplication>4.0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Al-Jazeera journalist detained in Berlin accuses Germany of colluding with repressive Sisi regime</theme><text>Egyptian/British Ahmed Mansour, one of the most senior journalists on the channel's Arabic service, says Germany has dragged itself into Cairo's dirty game</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>International Yoga Day, in pictures</theme><text>In pics: Milions of people worldwide take part in the first International Day of Yoga</text><duplication>8.69565217391</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Charleston church to reopen for Sunday service after shooting</theme><text>Congregation expected to flock to Emanuel African Methodist Church in the historic US city, days after a gunman shot nine black members to death during a Bible study group</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>International Day of Yoga: Indian prime minister leads exercise</theme><text>Indian prime minister Narendi Modi leads an inaugural International Day of Yoga exercise in front of thousands in New Delhi</text><duplication>11.1111111111</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Charleston church massacre: Things we learned from shooter Dylann Roof's racist manifesto</theme><text>White supremacist charged with murder of nine people in a church in South Carolina was a admirer of neo-Nazis and wanted to 'destroy the Jewish identity'</text><duplication>5.26315789474</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>One dead, nine wounded in Detroit street party shooting</theme><text>Man aged 20 shot dead at a block party in Detroit, US, as nine people are left with either critical or serious injuries</text><duplication>4.87804878049</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Angelina Jolie visits Syrian refugee camp in Turkey</theme><text>Hollywood actress uses her high profile to draw attention to the plight of displaced people</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Charleston massacre: Republicans at odds over Confederate flag</theme><text>Mitt Romney and Jeb Bush say South Carolina should remove the Confederate flag from the statehouse but Ted Cruz disagrees</text><duplication>3.84615384615</duplication></news><news><channel>World news</channel><theme>Migrant crisis 'at new high' across Channel</theme><text>Number of migrants arriving at makeshift camps in Calais is 'definitely climbing'</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Death toll from tainted liquor in Mumbai rises to 94</theme><text>Illicit liquor is often spiked with chemicals such as pesticides to increase its potency.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Man arrested after flight diverted to Northern Ireland</theme><text>Authorities have arrested a 42-year-old man for endangering the safety of a plane after a United Airlines flight from Rome to Chicago was forced to divert to Northern Ireland.</text><duplication>97.7777777778</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>New-agers and revelers descend on Stonehenge to mark summer solstice</theme><text>Visitors kissed the stones, dancers swirled on the grass and drummers pounded as part of the free-form celebrations.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Charleston church holds first service since deadly attack</theme><text>Members of a historic black church worshipped at their sanctuary Sunday for the first time since a gunman opened fire at a Bible study, killing nine people.</text><duplication>16.6666666667</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>1 dead, 9 wounded in shooting at Detroit block party attended by families</theme><text>Someone opened fire at a neighbourhood block party on a basketball court in Detroit Saturday, a barbecue attended by families with some small children in strollers.</text><duplication>27.9069767442</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>&#8216;Do you pray?': Syrians, Iraqis describe nation of fear inside ISIS realm</theme><text>There is no safe way out. People vanish - their disappearance sometimes explained by an uninformative death certificate, or worse, a video of their beheading.</text><duplication>6.89655172414</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Suspect in shooting death of New Orleans police officer arrested</theme><text>The arrest follows a 24-hour manhunt for Boys, who escaped from the vehicle after allegedly shooting and killing Officer Daryle Holloway.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Al-Jazeera journalist to remain in German custody</theme><text>A prominent Al-Jazeera journalist will remain in German custody for a second night, prosecutors said Sunday, saying they have not yet decided whether to extradite him to Egypt or set him free.</text><duplication>12.2448979592</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Neighbors but not friends: Japan, South Korea meet ahead of anniversary of ties</theme><text>Ministers from Japan and South Korea are due to hold a rare meeting on the eve of the 50th anniversary since their countries normalized relations marred by Japan's colonization and WWII conquest.</text><duplication>60.7142857143</duplication></news><news><channel>Global News : World</channel><theme>Economic turmoil has come to a head in Greece, again</theme><text>With the clock running down on Greece's chances of avoiding a painful exit from the euro, the country got a temporary lifeline to help it cope with a bank deposit drain.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Yemeni rebels persist even as their home region is destroyed in war</theme><text>SANAA, Yemen &#8212; Yemen&#8217;s Houthi rebels are enduring fierce bombing raids in their northern strongholds, as a Saudi-led campaign pounds neighborhoods, markets and power facilities, according to residents and aid workers.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>How climate-change doubters lost a papal fight</theme><text>VATICAN CITY &#8212; Pope Francis was about to take a major step backing the science behind &#173;human-driven global warming, and Philippe de Larminat was determined to change his mind. A French doubter who authored a book arguing that solar activity &#8212; not greenhouse gases &#8212; was driving global warming, de Larminat sought a spot at a climate summit in April sponsored by the Vatican&#8217;s Pontifical Academy of Sciences. Nobel laureates would be there. So would U.N. Secretary General Ban Ki-moon, U.S. economist Jeffrey Sachs and others calling for dramatic steps to curb carbon emissions.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>1.81818181818</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Will Israel protect Druze in the Golan from Syrian rebels?</theme><text>MAJDAL SHAMS, Golan Heights &#8212; From their hilltop cherry orchards, members of Israel&#8217;s minority Druze population come to watch and worry about their cousins in Syria, whose towns just a few miles away are now surrounded by jihadist rebels.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: 17 ways the unprecedented migrant crisis is reshaping our world</theme><text>The&#160;world is undergoing a dramatic, perhaps unprecedented migrant crisis. All around the globe, people are fleeing war zones, persecutions, or economic instability in search of a better life. They are undertaking perilous journeys and many are dying in huge numbers. Those that make it to their destination often face anxious, sometimes even outright hostile hosts.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: This journalist didn&#8217;t just interview North Korean defectors, he followed them on their escape</theme><text>North Korea is not the &#8220;Hermit Kingdom&#8221; it once was. After two decades of defections and the more recent arrival of cellphone technology, we now know much more about North Korea than we did in years past. Which is not to say that we know a lot. North Korea remains the world&#8217;s most isolated state, and the inner workings of Kim Jong Un&#8217;s regime remain a mystery, with reports about the goings on in Pyongyang difficult, if not impossible, to verify.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Western firms are doing business in Russia again, but it&#8217;s not going so well</theme><text>ST. PETERSBURG &#8212; As the crisis in Ukraine was spiraling into war a year ago, the Obama administration pressured U.S. business leaders not to attend Russia&#8217;s glitzy annual business summit. This year, they were back &#8212; but with Russia&#8217;s economy entering a deep funk, few of them were doing much business.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>2.12765957447</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>An Afghan jihadist&#8217;s life and death in Iraq: &#8216;They misused his innocence&#8217;</theme><text>KABUL &#8212; As he listened, Wali Mohammad Darwazi&#8217;s worst fears came true. His 23-year-old son, Mohammad Rafi, had vanished two months before with several former classmates from Kabul University. Now, Darwazi was on the phone with one of the classmates, whom he had reached in Syria. Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Netanyahu refuses to apologize for ex-ambassador&#8217;s criticism of Obama</theme><text>JERUSALEM &#8212; If there was any lingering doubt that President Obama and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu are estranged, now comes fresh evidence the two leaders and their proxies are engaged in a remarkably nasty, seriously personal tit-for-tat about who did whom wrong over the past six years.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>5.6338028169</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Yemen peace talks end without agreement &#8212; or a cease-fire</theme><text>BEIRUT &#8212; Peace talks in Geneva to halt the war in Yemen ended Friday without agreement as the United Nations appealed for $1.6&#160;billion in emergency aid to avert a humanitarian catastrophe in the Arabian Peninsula country.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>3.44827586207</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: Julian Assange&#8217;s sojourn in Ecuadorian Embassy has cost British taxpayers more than $17 million</theme><text>For&#160;Julian Assange, Wikileaks founder, this week marked three years of life in the confines of the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, where he sought asylum&#160;to avoid being extradited to Sweden on&#160;allegations of sexual assault, &#160;and where he has remained since.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: How International Yoga Day got India all bent out of shape</theme><text>Last year, when Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi delivered&#160;his maiden speech before the United Nations, he spoke of one of his country&#8217;s best known cultural exports in lofty terms. &#8220;Yoga is an invaluable gift of our ancient tradition," he said. "It is not about exercise but to discover oneness within yourself, the world and nature.&#8221; He used the&#160;occasion to propose an International Yoga Day, eventually supported by 177 countries and ratified by the United Nations last year. It's all part of Modi's hope to rebrand India's yoga to the world.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>5.94059405941</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Greece and Europe look into the abyss, with one last chance looming</theme><text>LONDON &#8211; After five years of precarious dancing at the cliff&#8217;s edge, Greece and Europe were perhaps just a weekend away Friday from a tumble into the unknown, with an emergency summit Monday seen as the last chance to avoid a potentially catastrophic breakup.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: Osama bin Laden&#8217;s son asked the U.S. government for his father&#8217;s death certificate. The U.S. said no.</theme><text>According to a recently leaked document, the son of al-Qaeda mastermind Osama bin Laden,&#160;Abdullah bin Laden, sent a letter to the U.S. Embassy in Saudi Arabia&#160;to ask for his father's death certificate.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>4.34782608696</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: The strange journey of Napoleon&#8217;s penis</theme><text>This week marked the bicentenary of the Battle of Waterloo. The epic clash&#160;saw the final defeat of the French emperor Napoleon, who, despite his supposedly "diminutive"&#160;stature, was&#160;a bogeyman for British children, a military genius for the ages, and a towering figure on the world stage.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: North Korea claims it can cure MERS (and a whole bunch of other things)</theme><text>TOKYO &#8212; North Korea has made some wacky claims over the years &#8212; like the one about discovering unicorns&#160;and the photos showing Kim Jong Un at the top of a snow-capped Mount Paekdu, which would have you believe he apparently climbed in dress shoes. And don&#8217;t forget that time his father, Kim Jong Il, reportedly&#160;hit&#160;five holes-in-one the first time he played&#160;golf.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>2.46913580247</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>WorldViews: This German politician lost an election, but won&#8217;t stop showing up for work</theme><text>When European Parliament member Bernd Posselt failed to get reelected last year, he simply decided to ignore the election results. One week after his defeat, the 59-year-old entered the European Union's legislative building&#160;in Strasbourg as if nothing had happened -- and has done so, ever since.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>4.0404040404</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Iraq chased Islamic State out of Tikrit. Getting residents back is still a battle.</theme><text>TIKRIT, Iraq &#8212; Snaking past blackened shop fronts and shattered homes, buses ferried the first civilian residents back to Tikrit this week, an initial step toward reviving this city after Islamic State militants were expelled more than two months ago. Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>3.77358490566</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>New U.N. report says world&#8217;s refugee crisis is worse than anyone expected</theme><text>LONDON &#8212; The number of people uprooted from their homes by war and persecution in 2014 was larger than in any year since detailed record-keeping began, according to a comprehensive report released early Thursday by the U.N. refugee agency that will add to the evidence of a global exodus unlike any in modern times.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>3.22580645161</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>New U.N. report says world&#8217;s refugee crisis is worse than anyone expected</theme><text>LONDON &#8212; The number of people uprooted from their homes by war and persecution in 2014 was larger than in any year since detailed record-keeping began, according to a comprehensive report released early Thursday by the U.N. refugee agency that will add to the evidence of a global exodus unlike any in modern times.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>3.22580645161</duplication></news><news><channel>World: World News, International News, Foreign Reporting - The Washington Post</channel><theme>Release of encyclical reveals pope&#8217;s deep dive into climate science</theme><text>VATICAN CITY &#8212; He warns of &#8220;synthetic agrotoxins&#8221; harming birds and insects and &#8220;bioaccumulation&#8221; from industrial waste. He calls for renewable fuel subsidies and &#8220;maximum energy efficiency.&#8221; And although he offers prayers at the beginning and end of his heavily anticipated missive on the environment, Pope Francis unmasks himself not only as a very green pontiff, but also as a total policy wonk.Read full article &amp;#62;&amp;#62;</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Netanyahu Rejects &#8216;International Diktat&#8217; on Israeli-Palestinian Peace Deal</theme><text>The prime minister of Israel said the international efforts failed to address his country&#8217;s security needs and other national interests.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>In China, Illegal Drugs Are Sold Online in an Unbridled Market</theme><text>Authorities have shown little interest in seriously regulating clandestine labs, turning China into a leading producer and exporter of synthetic drugs.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Journalist for Al Jazeera Held in Germany Awaits Verdict on Egyptian Arrest Warrant</theme><text>Ahmed Mansour is one of many figures whose arrest and extradition Cairo has demanded. His lawyers said the charges were politically motivated.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Op-Ed Contributor: Denmark's Far-Right Kingmakers</theme><text>The Danish People's Party triumphed by deftly blending xenophobia with a defense of the welfare state.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Tell Us How Your Church Addressed the Pope&#8217;s Encyclical</theme><text>The Times wants to know how places of worship in the United States and around the world are responding to Francis&#8217; message on the environment and climate change.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Tells Us How Your Church Addressed the Pope&#8217;s Encyclical</theme><text>The Times wants to know how places of worship in the United States and around the world are responding to Francis&#8217; message on the environment and climate change.</text><duplication>5.40540540541</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Cables Released by WikiLeaks Reveal Saudis&#8217; Checkbook Diplomacy</theme><text>The revelations appear in a trove of documents said to have come from inside the Saudi Ministry of Foreign Affairs and released by the group WikiLeaks.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Roadside Bomb Kills at Least 12 Afghans on Their Way Home</theme><text>The blast occurred in the Marja district of Helmand Province, a Taliban stronghold, killing at least 12 members of a family and wounding eight.</text><duplication>5.88235294118</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Assailants Target Police in Burundi</theme><text>Eleven police officers were wounded overnight when gunmen hurled grenades and attacked police stations across Bujumbura, Burundi&#8217;s capital.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Al Jazeera Journalist Detained in Germany</theme><text>Responding to an Egyptian arrest warrant, the authorities detained Ahmed Mansour at Berlin&#8217;s Tegel airport.</text><duplication>7.69230769231</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Car Bombing in Yemen&#8217;s Capital Kills at Least 2</theme><text>The attack on a mosque wounded at least six people, and the Islamic State&#8217;s Yemeni affiliate claimed responsibility.</text><duplication>5.12820512821</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Attack Gave Chinese Hackers Privileged Access to U.S. Systems</theme><text>Undetected for nearly a year, Chinese intruders executed a sophisticated hack that gave them &#8220;administrator privileges&#8221; in government networks. Their ultimate target: information on anyone seeking a security clearance.</text><duplication>3.44827586207</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Suit Has South Korea Looking Anew at Its Hard Line on Prostitution</theme><text>The case follows a landmark decision that decriminalized adultery, and reflects continuing changes in the nation&#8217;s social attitudes toward sex.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Opinion: The Chinese Want Their Art Back</theme><text>The government, state-run companies, private collectors and even some criminals are all trying to return antiquities to China.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>13 Arrested in China After Clashes With Police</theme><text>The police in a southern Chinese township arrested 13 people who illegally detained officials and police officers and stormed a police station and a government building in a dispute over a young woman&#8217;s death.</text><duplication>4.7619047619</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Gaza Welcomes Break From Strife and Reopening of Border With Egypt</theme><text>First, Egypt opened its border crossing, suggesting a thaw in relations between the Egyptian government and Hamas, and then news emerged that Hamas had begun quiet negotiations with Israel to extend a truce.</text><duplication>3.84615384615</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Maraj&#243; Island Journal: To Soften Image, Brazilian Police Ride In Atop Horned Beasts</theme><text>&#8220;Being the guy on the buffalo makes me more approachable, making my job a little bit easier,&#8221; is how one officer in Maraj&#243;, Brazil, explained it.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>For Faithful, Social Justice Goals Demand Action on Environment</theme><text>Many faith traditions are awakening to the burden that climate change is placing on poor people, and finding justification for caring for the environment in their scripture.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Toxic Liquor in India Kills at Least 84</theme><text>The dead lived in a Mumbai-area slum, and the toll was expected to rise. More than 30 people were hospitalized, many in serious condition, the police said.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news><news><channel>NYT &gt; World</channel><theme>Op-Ed Contributor: Pope Francis&#8217; Climate Error</theme><text>To control emissions, a carbon market is best.</text><duplication>0</duplication></news></data>